Guide to the Carol Fennelly papers, 1971-1997 MS2153
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Housing, 1984-1997; MS2153 Series 7; 6.75 Linear feet (Box 13, Box 15, Box 14, Box 17, Box 16, Box 12A, Box 22, Box 23, Box 20, Box 21, Box 18, Box 19)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors meeting agenda, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors meeting and status of activities, 11/15/1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Trustees meeting agendas, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Bylaws, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Catholic Charities, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Catholic Charities correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Christ House Information Board of Trustees meeting agendas and updates for, 11/15/1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Church based shelter money, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Commission on Mental Health money, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Community Trusts for Affordable Housing, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors Information for Community Housing Trust, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Proposal to the Community Partnership for the Prevention of Homelessness, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Revised Proposal from the TAH to the Community Partnership for the Prevention of Homelessness, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Proposal to Community Partnership for the Prevention of Homelessness, 08/18/1994 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Proposal to the Community Partnership for the Prevention of Homelessness, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing: Faxes from the Community Preservation and Development Corporation, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Consultants and Grant Agreements, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Cornerstone funding alert and project summaries, 05/1994 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Correspondence to the Board of Directors, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Correspondence to the Board of Trustees, 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing DC Government Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing D.C. Initiative: Working together to solve homelessness Executive summary, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Emergency shelter grant, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Enterprise Housing Financial Services consultants contract (drafts), undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Miscellaneous financial information, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Finances, 1991-1996 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Financial report summary, 07/1994 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Housing, undated (Box 21)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Financial statements and reports, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing F-O-C Crew, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing FOIA request to Metropolitan Police dept., undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Forgivable loan policy, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing General information overview, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Grand opening and dedication invitations, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Grant applications, agendas, and correspondence, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Lisa Green transition of..., undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Interim report to the Board of Trustees, 03/24/1992 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Interim report to the Board of Trustees, 09/02/1992 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Interim report to the Board of Trustees, 03/12/1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Jeremiah House, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Jeremiah House, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Jeremiah House, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Job announcement, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Housing, undated (Box 22)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Kairos House Payment application #9 review, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Kairos House, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Trust for Affordable Housing Letter to "60 Minutes" from Howrey and Simon, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing letterhead proof and logos, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Loan applications, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Loan, grant, and consultant resolutions, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Loan and grant requests, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Loan requests, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Marshall Heights Tour, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Membership to Board of Directors and agenda for Community for Creative Non-Violence, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Memorandum of understanding between D.C., U.S., HUD and the Community Partnership for the Prevention of Homelessness, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing meeting minutes, 11/16/1994 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing meeting [January], undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing meeting minutes, 07/17/1996 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing meeting minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing meeting minutes and memorandum, 08/1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing minutes, 07/01/1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing special meeting, 07/25/1994 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing national conference on homelessness information, 04/18/1994 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Press releases, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Roy Price reception, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Request for proposal, 12/21/1992 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Ribbon cutting and ground breaking, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing report draft, 1992-12/31/1993 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing report, 1992-12/31/1993 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Status report, 05/22/1993 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing report, 1994-12/31/1995 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing report, 1995-12/31/1996 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing report draft, 1995-12/31/1996 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Samaritan Inns, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Single room occupancy court, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Single room occupancy court, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Single room occupancy miscellaneous, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Housing, undated (Box 23)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Single room occupancy Dixon letter, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Single room occupancy preliminary information, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Tabitha's house directions, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Veronica's house, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Vince Gray trailers communications, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Winston Resignation, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Newspaper articles, 1974-1993; MS2153 Series 8; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 23)
  This series contains newspaper articles relate to the work of Carol Fennelly and the Community for Creative Non-Violence. The articles date from 1974-93.
  - Newspaper articles, undated (Box 23)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1974-1981 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper articles:, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Publicity and publications, 1979-1987; MS2153 Series 9; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 24)
  This series contains brochures, press releases, flyers, articles, a calendar papers, reports, manuals, and manuscripts. The materials date from 1979-87. The materials cover the topics of homeless shelters, the movie "Samaritan", and hunger in America.
  - Publicity and publications, undated (Box 24)
  - Brochures: by CCNV, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Brochures: CCNV's last brochure, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Brochures: not by CCNV, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Flyers: numerous subjects, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases: Census, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases: Fasts, 1979-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases: Fundraisers, 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases: Holidays, 1983-1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases: Hunger in the Land of Plenty, 06/20/1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases: Initiative 17, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases: METRO, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases: Miscellaneous topics, 1978-1989 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases: Movies: Samaritan and Promises to Keep, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases: Protests, 1975-1991 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases: Shelter, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases: Winter, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Articles: "Anatomy of a Prison Strike" by John Bach and Mitchell Snyder Liberation Magazine, 05/1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Articles: "I was Homeless, and You Gave Me Shelter" Mary Ellen Hombs and Mitch Snyder Christianity and Crisis, 02/21/1983 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Calendar: Produced by CCNV, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Manuals: "Managing the Media: A Guide for Activists by Carol Fennelly, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Manuals: "Reaching out: A Manual for Shelter Volunteers" CCNV, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Manuscripts: "The Community for Creative Non-Violence" Josh Daniel (book), undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Manuscripts: "A Signal Through the Flames" Chapters 8-14 Victoria Rader, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Papers: A Strategy for Helping America's Homeless" The Heritage Foundation, 05/06/1985 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Papers: "CCNV Working Paper on Low-Income Housing", 09/15/1987 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Papers: "Homelessness in Washington, D.C.: An Overview of Current Conditions and Events" Mary Ellen Hombs, 02/02/1985 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Papers: "Social Recognition of the Homeless: Policies of Indifference: Mary Ellen Hombs, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Report: "A Forced March to Nowhere" Mary Ellen Hombs and Mitch Snyder, 09/01/1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Speaking engagements, 1986-1990; MS2153 Series 10; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 25, Box 25A)
  This series contains invitations and other materials related to the speaking engagements of Mitch Snyder. These documents date from 1986-90. These materials are primarily from universities, public libraries, and community groups.
  - Speaking Engagements, undated (Box 25)
  - Mitch Snyder: Americans for Democratic Action speaker, 02/05/1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mitch Snyder: Bates College, 02/08/1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Mitch Snyder: Housing California A Vision for the Decade, 04/02/1990--04/03/1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mitch Snyder: Canadian Conference The International Year of Shelter for the Homeless, 09/13/1987-09/16/1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mitch Snyder: Colorado College, 04/18/1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Mitch Snyder: Concordia College, 09/18/1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Mitch Snyder: Concordia College Faith, Reason, and World Affairs Symposium Homeless in America, 09/18/1988-09/20/1988 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Mitch Snyder: Denison University, 10/04/1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Mitch Snyder: Georgetown University Equal Justice Foundation (EJF), 03/20/1990 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Mitch Snyder: The Human Tree, Inc Beverly Hills, CA, 08/12/1987 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Mitch Snyder: Illinois AFL-CIO, 04/04/1990 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Mitch Snyder: Jersey City Public Library Perspective on Homeless, 10/23/1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Mitch Snyder: John Carroll University, 08/16/1989 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Mitch Snyder: Jersey City Public Library, 08/07/1989 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Mitch Snyder: Legal Defense Center, Inc., 02/1990-04/21/1989 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Mitch Snyder: Lou Douglas Lectures Myth and Reality, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Mitch Snyder: Loyola Union "Mitch Snyder Champion of the Homeless", 04/07/1988 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Mitch Snyder: Minnesota Community Action Agency, 02/14/1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Mitch Snyder: Morristown, NJ, Junior League of Morristown, Inc., 11/14/1989 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Mitch Snyder: Ohio Unity Conference II Low Income People Together (LIPT), 08/28/1987 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Mitch Snyder: Ohio University Bonsai B'rith Hillel Foundation, 04/24/1990 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mitch Snyder: Perdue University The Catholic Center at Perdue, 01/25/1990 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Mitch Snyder: Radford College, 04/04/1990 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Mitch Snyder: Richmond Commission on Human Relations (included Mary Ellen Hombs), 05/03/1985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Mitch Snyder: Rotary Club of Washington, D.C., 02/21/1990 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Mitch Snyder: Share our Strength, 11/15/1989 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Mitch Snyder: St. Norbert College "Homeless in America", 02/26/1986 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Mitch Snyder: Syracuse Homeless Project, 02/5/1988 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Mitch Snyder: The Tenderloin Times, 07/26/1989 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Mitch Snyder: Tulsa Chapter of the Young Presidents' Organization (YPO), 06/20/1989 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Mitch Snyder: Tulsa City-County Library System Alfred E. Aaronson lecture series, 04/07/1990 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Mitch Snyder: Washington-Greene Community Action Corporation, 02/22/1990-02/23/1990 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: American University, 01/28/1987 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Amherst College, 12/06/1988 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Association of American Colleges, 02/29/1988 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Attleboro Area Youth and Family Services, Inc., 08/12/1987 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Center City Ministries re: Lehigh University, 12/19/1989 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Commission on Human Concerns, 02/19/1987 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: District of Columbia Court of Appeals, 11/05/1987 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: District of Columbia Occupational Therapy Assoc., 09/29/1987 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Duke University student action cooperative, 02/11/1988 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Hark Homes Holistic Housing for the Homeless NY, 06/02/1987 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Joseph's House Shelter of Troy, Inc. Troy, NY, 10/05/1987 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Morningside Emergency Shelter Brattleboro, VT, 10/29/1986 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: National Tenants Organization, inc., 09/12/1986 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: National Urban Coalition, 02/09/1987 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: The Open Door Community Atlanta, GA, 05/21/1987 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Teens Opposing Poverty (TOP), 02/29/1988 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Speaking Engagements, undated (Box 25A)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Santa Clara University, 03/1990 (Box 25A, Folder 1)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Stanford University speakers bureau, 08/21/1987 (Box 25A, Folder 2)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Star of Hope Ministries Texas, 09/19/1986 (Box 25A, Folder 3)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Union Mission, Inc./Grace House Savannah George, 12/18/1987 (Box 25A, Folder 4)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Wayne County Neighborhood Legal Services, MI, 10/20/1988 (Box 25A, Folder 5)
  - Invitations to Mitch Snyder: Wesleyan University Middletown, CT, 03/03/1988 (Box 25A, Folder 6)
  - Other speakers: CCNV sponsored Sunday Series, 1983-1984 (Box 25A, Folder 7)
  - Other speakers: Carol Fennelly [Capitol Hill Group Ministry], 09/18/1980 (Box 25A, Folder 8)
- Speeches, 1985-1989; MS2153 Series 11; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 25A)
  This series contains speeches written and presented by Mitch Snyder. These speeches date from 1985-89. Many are note dated.
  - Speeches, undated (Box 25A)
  - Mitch Snyder speech, undated (Box 25A, Folder 9)
  - Mitch Snyder speech, undated (Box 25A, Folder 10)
  - Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 25A, Folder 11)
  - Mitch Snyder additional speeches, undated (Box 25A, Folder 12)
  - Mitch Snyder handwritten speeches, undated (Box 25A, Folder 13)
  - Mitch Snyder "old speech", 1985 (Box 25A, Folder 14)
  - Mitch Snyder "old speech", 1986 (Box 25A, Folder 15)
  - Mitch Snyder, 1988-1989 (Box 25A, Folder 16)
- Subject files, 1977-1993; MS2153 Series 12; 5.75 Linear feet (Box 35, Box 34, Box 33, Box 32, Box 31, Box 30, Box 29, Box 28, Box 27, Box 26, Box 33A, Box 36)
  This series contains among many document types items related to census materials, biographical data, and statements. These materials date from 1977-93. This series is composed of materials collected and created by the Mitch Snyder, Carol Fennelly and the Community for Creative Non-Violence during the work performed on behalf of homeless people in Washington, D.C. and other activist causes.
  - Subject files, undated (Box 26)
  - About CCNV, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Art Work, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Bibliography, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Biography for Carol Fennelly, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Biography for Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Biography for Mitch Snyder Autobiography typed original with comments by Mary Ellen Hombs, 12/1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Biography Mitch Snyder Power of Attorney and Last Will and Testament, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Biography Mitch Snyder renaming of street "Mitch Snyder Place", 08/14/1993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Biography Mitch Snyder study notes from various books (long hand originals), undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Census 1990 count of homeless (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Census 1990 count of homeless (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Corpus Christi submarine naming controversy correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Corpus Christi submarine naming controversy lists, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 27)
  - Corpus Christi submarine naming controversy, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Corpus Christi submarine naming controversy visitor log [April], undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Education Cornell University visit, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Facts and statistics re: homeless in America, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fasting, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Fasting miscellaneous, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - F.O.I.A. requests, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Food salvaging Congressional luncheon, 07/18/1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Food salvaging correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Food salvaging Giant Boycott, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Food salvaging Hunger in the Land of Plenty a most unusual luncheon, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Food salvaging Hunger in the Land of Plenty, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Food salvaging Miscellaneous documents, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Holidays Christmas event at Convention Center, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 28)
  - Holidays Christmas Christmas Eve dinner, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Holidays Christmas Christmas Eve party, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Holidays Christmas Christmas Eve party, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Holidays Good Friday, 1987-1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Holidays Thanksgiving, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Holidays Thanksgiving, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Homeless: "A Study of Fifty Homeless Men", 1913 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Hypothermia, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Initiative 17 bumper sticker, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Initiative 17 Committee to Save Initiative 17 financial records, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Initiative 17 correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Initiative 17 Election results, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Initiative 17 Information, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Initiative 17 Petition, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Initiative 17 Referendum 005, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Initiative 17 Reference pack, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Initiative 17 Save Initiative 17 organization, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Initiative 17 Voter survey, 06/21/1990 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 29)
  - Lists A & B Musical Groups, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Lists Atlantic Life Communication (Activists), undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Lists Call to Prayer, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Lists Cartoonists, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Lists Celebrity, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Lists COHHO, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Lists College Activists (F-file), undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Lists Funeral Call List, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Lists Key contacts for campaign, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Lists Media, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Lists Metropolitan Washington Council Executive Board, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Lists miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Lists miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Lists miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Lists Peace Corps meeting, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Lists Older National Call List, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Lists Volunteer Lawyers, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Lists Washington Redskins Players, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Homelessness, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 30)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Homelessness, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Homelessness, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death correspondence, 07/10/1990-10/15/1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death correspondence, 04/1990-07/09/1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death correspondence, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death donations in his name, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 31)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Funeral, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Obituaries, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Recording of memorial service, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Sympathy cards, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Sympathy cards, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 32)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Sympathy cards, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)